# Yoan ROULEAU

## Web developer

I'm a 21 years old french which has always been interested in IT and media creation. Armed with a no-limits imagination, my objective is to become a Web developer, because it perfectly matches my passion for IT and my creative spirit.





Yoan.Rouleau@etu.univ-smb.fr

+33(0) 7 50 89 16 29



Annecy, France



4 Nov. 1999

#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

## Web Developper (Sandwich course)

#### Merci Creative

Since July 2020

Bourg-Saint-Maurice, France

- Taking part in various web development projects for many Savoie businesses, mostly using Wordpress
- Projects are developed using different frameworks and technologies within plurilanguages teams

#### **Order Picker**

## Lactalis Logistique

October 2018 to August 2019

Saint-Vulbas, France

- Picking, stacking and elaborating orders for many differents national warhouses.
- Respecting and applicating hygienes standards.

## Web Developper (Internship)

### French Institute of Pondicherry

April 2019 to June 2019

Pondicherry, India

- Creation of the new institutional website of the institute.
   Website built with Wordpress and the Elementor Pro and Toolset plugins.
- Taking part in an IT project with english-talking members

#### **EDUCATION**

## LP DIM

Professional Bachelor's Degree in multi-platform software development

USMB / IUT Annecy – Annecy, France

2020-2021

#### **DUETI Informatique**

2-semesters Exchange program: Bachelor of Science in applied computing

Letterkenny Institute of Technology – Letterkenny, Ireland

2017-2019

## **DUT Informatique**

2-year University degree in computer science USMB / IUT Annecy – Annecy, France

2017-2019

#### French Baccalaureate STI2D

High School diploma specialized in science and computer engineering

\*Plaine de l'Ain High School – Ambérieu, France 2014-2017

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

	Average			Good	i	Great		
Web front-end	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>O</b>	0	
Web back-end	<b>()</b>	<b>O</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>O</b>	<b>(</b>	0	
Software engineering	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>O</b>	0	0	
Database management	<b>(</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>O</b>	0	0	0	

### **HUMAN SKILLS**

Teamwork	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>O</b>	0
Problem solving	<b>(</b>	<u></u>	<b>(</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>O</b>	0	0
Adaptability	<b>O</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>O</b>	<b>()</b>	0	<b>O</b>	0
Critical thinking	<b>O</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>(</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	0	0

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

- I have learnt to work within multilingual and complex workflows
- I am used to work on different projects at the same time
- I experienced stressful tasks and I am now able to take a step back during tough situations

#### **LANGUAGES**

French	<b>O</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>O</b>	<b>()</b>
English	<b>O</b>	<b>O</b>	<b>(</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>()</b>	<b>O</b>	0
German				0	0	0	$\overline{C}$

#### INTERESTS

- I like playing videogames with my friends during my free time
- I'm a paraglider and planes enjoyer. Living in the Alpes helps a lot for those hobbies!
- I'm also interested in various martial arts, and have been practicing judo and iaido for a long time
- I like to travel a lot. I've been trying to travel as much as I can during my studies.

# **REFERENCES**

## **David Morille**

CEO at Merci Creative, We are Merci group davidmorille@wearemerci.com

## **Luc Damas**

Associate professor to IT Department at University of Savoy *luc.damas@univ-smb.fr*